Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Software, Series 1
  - Games, Subseries 1.4
    - Data East USA, Inc. Express Raiders, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 190)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Heavy Barrel, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - Data East USA, Inc. High Seas Havoc, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Ikari Warriors, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 158)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Karnov, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 31)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Karnov, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 158)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Kung Fu Master, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 31)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Kung Fu Master/ Karate Champ, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 31)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Lock 'N' Chase, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Lock 'N' Chase, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Lock 'N' Chase, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 219)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Nail 'n Scale, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Night Stalker, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 219)
    - Data East USA, Inc. RoboCop, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Data East USA, Inc. RoboCop, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - Data East USA, Inc. RoboCop, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeTandy (Box 217)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Tac-Scan, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 134)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Tag team wrestling, 1986, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Data East USA, Inc. ........tion (the label is torn), n.d., 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Data East USA, Inc. TumblePop, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Victory Road, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 158)
    - Data East USA, Inc. Werewolf: The Last Warrior, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - Data Equipment Supply Corporation Vic-Ville, n.d., 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - DataBioTics, Inc. Black Hole, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeTexas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 93)
    - DataEast Burger Time, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 204)
    - DataEast Commando, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 169)
    - DataEast Guerrilla, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 169)
    - DataEast Karate Champ, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 204)
    - DataEast Tag Team Wrestling!!!!!, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 169)
    - Datamost, Inc. Aztec, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 191)
    - Datamost, Inc. Cohen's Towers, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 135)
    - Datamost, Inc. Mr. Robot and his Robot Factory, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - Datamost, Inc. Mr. Robot and his Robot Factory, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 182)
    - Datamost, Inc. My Chess II, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Datamost, Inc. Round About, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 198)
    - Datamost, Inc. Super Bunny, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - DataSoft, Inc. 221 B Baker St., 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 191)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Alternate Reality The Cit'y, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 142)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Alternate Reality: The Dungeon, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 89)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Bishop's Square/ Maxwell's Demon, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 79)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Bismarck: The North Sea chase, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 176)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Black Magic, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Black Magic, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 186)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Bob Bishop's Dung Beetles, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Canyon Climber, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Clowns and Balloons, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 127)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Clowns and Balloons, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 152)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Comic Relief Prof. Renegade to the Rescue, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Conan, 1984, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 79)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Conan, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 180)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Conan :Famous Faces, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Crosscheck, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 139)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Dig Dug, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Dig Dug, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - DataSoft, Inc. DigDug, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 175)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Force 7, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 203)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Global Commander, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Goonies, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Gunslinger, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 46)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Gunslinger, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Juno First, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 191)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Konami's Juno First, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 198)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Mercenary, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 75)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Mind Pursuit, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 185)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Mr. Do!, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 53)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Mr. Do!, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Pacific Coast Highway, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Pole Position!, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Rock-Ola's Nibbler, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 110)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Saracen, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Saracen, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 188)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Dallas Quest, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Goonies, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 148)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Hunt for Red October, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Neverending Story, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 53)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The NeverEnding Story, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 191)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Official Moon Shuttle, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Official Zaxxon by Sega, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - DataSoft, Inc. The Sands of Egypt, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Theatre Europe, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 58)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Theatre Europe, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Time and Magik, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Tom Clancy's The Hunt for Red October: The Software, 1984, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 96)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Tom Clancy's The Hunt for Red October: The Software, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Tomahawk: a helicopter simulation, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 158)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Tomahawk: a helicopter simulation, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 176)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Video Title Shop, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 91)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Zorro, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 38)
    - DataSoft, Inc. Zorro, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Read: Speed Reader II, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 115)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Word Attack! Word, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 143)
    - Davka Corporation The Philistine Ploy, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 54)
    - DBR Limited Battle of Britain Classic War Series, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - DBR Limited Falklands 82 Classic War Series, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Deadly Games The Battle of Britain: the greatest air battle in history, 1991, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Macintosh (Box 5)
    - Designing Minds Poco Man The Game, 1989, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 104)
    - DesignStar Consultants, Inc. Omni-play Basketball, 1989, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 180)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Spellagraph: a revealing spelling game, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - DesignWare, Inc. The Notable Phantom, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - DIC Animation City, Inc. Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Digital Concepts Torch 2081, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 101)
    - Digital Illusions Seaworthy: Two WWII SImulators on One CD-ROM, 1994, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 12)
    - Digitek Inc Final Mission, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 74)
    - DigiTek, Inc. Hollywood Poker!, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 31)
    - Digitek, Inc. Hollywood Poker!, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 104)
    - Dinamic Grand Prix Master, endorsed by Jorge Martinez "Aspar", n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 102)
    - DiNAMiC Narco Police, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - Dinamic Navy Moves, 1989, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 104)
    - Dinamic PNavy Moves Version Demo copy, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 146)
    - Discovery Software International, Inc. Arkanoid, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 104)
    - Discovery Software International, Inc. Hybris, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Discovery Software International, Inc. Sword of Sodan, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Discovery Software International, Inc. Zoom!, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Discovery Software International, Inc. Zoom!, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Disney Software Disney's Ariel The Little Mermaid, 1992, computer cartridgeSEGA Genesis (Box 6)
    - Disney Software Duck Tales: The quest for gold, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 15)
    - Disney Software Goofy's Railway Express, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 162)
    - Disney Software Mickey & Minnie's FunTime Print Kit, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 220)
    - Distinctive Software, Inc. Dick Tracy: the crime-solving adventure, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 160)
    - Distro Enterprises, Inc. Her Majesty's Secret Weapon, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 168)
    - Dolphin Marine Systems, Inc. Assignment: Miami/ Code Name: Enforcer, 1990, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 168)
    - Domark Group, Ltd. Badlands, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 96)
    - Domark Group, Ltd. James Bond 007 in Live and Let Die: The Computer Game, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 101)
    - Domark Group, Ltd. Licence to Kill, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 99)
    - Domark Group, Ltd. Marko's Magic Football, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Domark Group, Ltd. Pictionary: The computer edition, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 99)
    - Domark Group, Ltd. Virtual Reality Studio, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 103)
    - Don't Ask Computer Software Wordrace, 1982, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 119)
    - Dorsett Educational Systems, Inc. Courseware: Basic Electricity, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 149)
    - Dorsett Educational Systems, Inc. Courseware: More Quadratics, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 149)
    - Double-Gold Software Rubik's Cube Unlocked, n.d., 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 119)
    - Dr. T's Music Software Dr. T's Sing-A-Long Kids' Classics, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 20)
    - Dragonware Ooze, 1989, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 147)
    - DreamWorks Fire Shark, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - DreamWorks Shove It!: The Warehouse Game, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - DreamWorks Target Earth, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - DTMC, Inc. Lazlo's Leap Puzzle Extraordinaire, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - DTMC Inc. Ranma 1/2: Hard Battle, 1991, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - DTMC, Inc. The Adventures of Dr. Franken, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 8)
    - Dynabyte Software Lease? Buy?, n.d., 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Dynabyte Software The Mortgage Comparer, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Dynacomp, Inc. Trivia Mania, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 170)
    - Dynamite Software [Sharedata, Inc.] Action Thrillers, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 186)
    - Dynamite Software [Sharedata, Inc.] Arcade Action, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 186)
    - Dynamite Software [Sharedata, Inc.] Interactive Adventures, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 186)
    - Dynamite Software [Sharedata, Inc.] Leisure Time Classics, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 186)
    - Dynamix, Inc. Betrayal At Krondor, 1994, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 12)
    - Dynamix, Inc. Nova 9, 1991, computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 163)
    - Dynamix, Inc. Red Baron: World War I Dogfighting Action, a Damon Slye simulation [includes A-10 Tank Killer], 1994, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 18)
    - Dynamix, Inc. Rise of the Dragon, 1994, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Sega (Box 207)
    - Dynamix, Inc. Stellar-fire, 1993, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Sega (Box 207)
    - Dynamix, Inc. The Adventures of Willy Beamish, 1993, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Sega (Box 207)
    - Earthware Services, Inc. Black Belt, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Earthware Services, Inc. Journey Into Darkness, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 185)
    - Earthware Services, Inc. Volcanoes, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 58)
    - Earthware Services, Inc. Wheeler Dealers, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 58)
    - EB Software TI- Runner, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Texas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - EBook, Inc. Beauty and the Beast, 1992, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 170)
    - Ebook, Inc. The Sleeping Beauty: A multimedia storybook, 1992, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 159)
    - Eden Prairie, MNLasersoft, Inc. Casino Action: 40 Vegas Style Action Games, 1995, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Macintosh (Box 5)
    - Educational Software, Inc. Dog Daze, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 152)
    - Educational Software Inc Space Games (2 copies), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Educational Software, Inc. Tricky Tutorial continuous demo disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - Educational Technologies, Inc. Bike Hike, computer cartridgeCommodore (Box 27)
    - Eduware Services, Inc. Metri-vert, 1979, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Eduware Services, Inc. Windfall, 1980, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 119)
    - Eidersoft Software, Ltd. Karate, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 41)
    - Eidersoft Software, Ltd. Metropolis, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 75)
    - Eidersoft Software Ltd ST Karate, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 77)
    - Electra Inc. Better Dead than Alien, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 27)
    - Electric Book Company Baby Animals, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 27)
    - Electric Dreams Software, Ltd. Incredible Shrinking Sphere, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 151)
    - Electric Dreams Software, Ltd. Spindizzy, 1986, 2 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Electric Dreams Software, Ltd. Spindizzy Worlds, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - Electric Dreams Software, Ltd. The Rocky Horror Picture Show, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Electric Dreams Software, Ltd. Upper Reaches of Apshai, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 96)
    - Electric Transit Co Lunar Explorer, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 65)
    - Electrobrain Corporation Brainbender, 1991, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Electrobrain Corporation Fist of the North Star, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 204)
    - Electrobrain Corporation Raiden Trad, 1992, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Electrobrain Corporation Stanley: The Search for Dr Livingston, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 204)
    - Electronic Arts 4-D Boxing, 1991, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Electronic Arts Age of Adventure, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - Electronic Arts Amnesia, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 122)
    - Electronic Arts Archon II: Adept, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 122)
    - Electronic Arts Archon: The Light and the dark, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 146)
    - Electronic Arts Arctic Fox, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Electronic Arts Arctic Fox, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - Electronic Arts Arctic Fox [Arcticfox], n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 101)
    - Electronic Arts Axis Assassin, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 132)
    - Electronic Arts Axis Assassin, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Electronic Arts B.O.B., 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Electronic Arts Bangkok Knights, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 146)
    - Electronic Arts Battlefront: Corps level command in World War II, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Electronic Arts Bill Budge Pinball Construction Set, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 201)
    - Electronic Arts Birds of Prey, 1993, ? computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 3)
    - Electronic Arts Budokan: the martial spirit, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 40)
    - Electronic Arts Caveman Ugh-lympics, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Electronic Arts Caveman Ugh-lympics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - Electronic Arts Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Simulator, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 174)
    - Electronic Arts Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Trainer, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 44)
    - Electronic Arts Chuck Yeager's Advanced Flight Trainer 2.0, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 61)
    - Electronic Arts Deathlord, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Electronic Arts Deathlord, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 117)
    - Electronic Arts Delta Patrol, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Electronic Arts Deluxe Productions, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 103)
    - Electronic Arts Deluxe Video Version Demo copy, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Electronic Arts Demon Stalkers, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Electronic Arts E.O.S. - Earth Orbit Stations, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 29)
    - Electronic Arts EA Air Force LHX Attack Chopper, 1992, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 207)
    - Electronic Arts F-117 Night Storm, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Electronic Arts F22 Interceptor: tactical fighter, 1991, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Electronic Arts Flood, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 104)
    - Electronic Arts Football, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Electronic Arts Hard Hat Mack, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 142)
    - Electronic Arts Hard Hat Mack, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 146)
    - Electronic Arts Haunting: starring Polterguy, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Electronic Arts Heart of Africa, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - Electronic Arts Instant Music, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 201)
    - Electronic Arts It's only rock 'n' roll, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 100)
    - Electronic Arts John Madden Football, 1992, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Electronic Arts John Madden Football '92, 1991, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Electronic Arts Jordan vs. Bird One on One, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Electronic Arts Julius Erving v. Larry Bird One-on-One, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 201)
    - Electronic Arts Labyrinth of Time, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 12)
    - Electronic Arts Lakers versus Celtics and the NBA Playoffs, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 159)
    - Electronic Arts Legacy of the Ancients, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 190)
    - Electronic Arts Lords of Conquest, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - Electronic Arts M.U.L.E., n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 33)
    - Electronic Arts Madden NFL '94, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Electronic Arts Mail Order Monsters, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 144)
    - Electronic Arts Make your own Murder Party, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 167)
    - Electronic Arts Make your own Murder Party: vol. 1: The big kill & Empire, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 128)
    - Electronic Arts Make your own Murder Party: vol. 1: The big kill & Empire, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 184)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness, 1989, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 4)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 117)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 137)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness, 1989, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - Electronic Arts Marble Madness [2 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Electronic Arts Mars Saga, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - Electronic Arts MLBPA Baseball, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 207)
    - Electronic Arts Movie Maker, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 146)
    - Electronic Arts Murder on the Zinderneuf, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 154)
    - Electronic Arts Music Construction Set, 1989, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 164)
    - Electronic Arts Mutant League Football (one of the ten best games on the Genesis...), 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Electronic Arts NATO Commander, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - Electronic Arts NHL Hockey, 1991, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Electronic Arts One-on-One Basketball with Julius "Dr. J" Erving and Larry Bird, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 140)
    - Electronic Arts One-on-One by Eric Hammond, Larry Bird, and Julius Erving Version Demo copy, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Electronic Arts One-on-One by Eric Hammond, Larry Bird, and Julius Erving Version Demo copy, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)